# RUEI-PU(Allen) KOU

# Front-End Developer

Three years solid experiences in building static websites(pages) including RWD, SPA. I launch projects quickly using frameworks like Bootstrap or SUSY. Now, I am interested in developing web apps using React and Redux for frontend, and NodeJs for backend. I have done some small projects like todo list binding with Firebase, and real-time chatting room by Socket.io. In addition, I am learning about popular tools and frameworks such as MongoDB, GraphQL, Meteor and React Native. As an F2E, I always follow the trend of the field and try to apply them to the next project.

## Skills

#### **Frontend**

- 3+ yrs HTML/ CSS (Sass)
- 1yr React/ Redux(Es6)

#### **Backend**

• 1yr NodeJs(Express, Socket.io)

#### Tools

• Webpack • Gulp • Git • Mocha

## Work experiences

### Front End Developer I DIGIM

Taipei, Taiwan I January 2014 to May 2014

- · Converted PSDs to web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- · Developed retina display friendly RWD pages
- · Collaborated with the creative and back-end teams
- Enhanced colleagues' developing performances by using Sass and HTML template(ERB)

## Web Developer I Rexholiday

Taipei, Taiwan I July 2013 to December 2013

- · Collaborated with stakeholders to improve an internal traveling system
- Developed internal IT devices plan
- Enhanced colleagues' workflow using SaaS

#### Web Developer I Webike.tw

Taipei, Taiwan I January 2013 to July 2013

- · Designed and developed the first version of prototype of eCommerce website base on Magento
- Organized over 300k primitive data to MySQL database
- Deployed project to EC2 instances in LAMP environment on AWS
- · Made back-up plans and optimized servers' performances

## Contact

imakou@gmail.com (905)-966-3228 Github/ Portfolio

## Education

Diploma in Computer Programmer Seneca College - Toronto, ON January 2015 to April 2017 Bachelor in Information management Hsing Wu University - Taipei, Taiwan August 2007 to August 2011

# **Activity**

#### Volunteer I Fa-Yi Chong-De Guang-Hui Association

Toronto, Canada I April 2014 to Present

- Assisted members to run meetings using live streaming platform
- Educated charity member on selection and implementation of electronic devices
- · Organizing meeting records and distributed records to members

